What are you doing with?
So, first time I will watch a record.
So, finally we set up Aboot's voice meter banana.
I guess.
Now, could it stream a quality level controls?
I thought we were doing an ebook rock.
This is the interrupt.
I'll cut a lot of votes by six.
I would talk about it partially over here.
I would talk about it.
I will talk.
You come here. Come back.
Aboot demonetized him.
Good old lady Aboot.
Respect your elders Aboot.
I'll respect you.
Look at this lady Rishi.
What will you do?
Shut up man.
You are already here.
That's a bad way.
I'll just make up.
This is the magic of makeup.
Why did you do this?
I am a subban.
I know you want to say true women's say help.
Look at me.
It's only because it's not true.
You know.
I can't express proper image.
Rishi, that's why you are flat.
Meanwhile, Roadhog will look over there.
Looking like Pakistan.
See.
Roadhog is eating champion.
I have picked out something.
I think I can do it.
Some left.
Meanwhile, Roadhog right.
Meanwhile, full team.
Where is it?
Okay.
It's a solution gone man.
I like how he's hiding.
He had that one filler over there.
Oh my god.
This is a nip.
Where is the other healer?
Is there another healer?
Roadhog.
He's left.
I'm watching you now.
Roadhog.
He had no other healer.
He's right.
Roadhog.
He's left.
Rai and Billa.
Nater.
Mercy, Nater.
Rai and Billa.
Rai and Nater.
I want it again.
I should go to my wedding.
He's right.
He's left.
I'm dead.
Oh.
Who from where and why?
Mac.
Mac and cheese.
Have you ever had spicy Mac and cheese?
That is fucking amazing.
Mac and cheese has to be normal.
it's dead
yeah yeah it's dead
it's high enough but i have to talk to you
i heard the high noon i'm looking at it
it's very dark
it's nothing to see it
i'm not sure if i'm high enough
that was an easy fight
it didn't realize it was that easy but
i know
we did a lot of work there
boy it's supposed to be a 10 minute video
it's supposed to be a 10 minute video
i don't know if i'm sorry
it's already 10 minute mark
i don't know i'm sorry
our setup included should be 10 minutes
i enjoyed
i think 10 minutes match 1 minute
the matches
oh god
sorry it's not here
that's not in
sorry sorry
i'm sorry
i will see
oh my god
i'm watching your back
then i have nothing to worry about
how did i remind you
i remember you're training
and we'll get through this
just for my back
you are recording
it's the second game
i got it
hello to the recording
i was just explaining how
sad this guy died
with how no clear
i got it
hey corner
hurry hurry
the ryan is to ryan's ghost
and this
this will heal
ryan is not that good this shield
like you didn't hear ryan's ghost
ryan's bang
hello and there
go forward to work
hello hello
yes and not you man
i was standing in front of him
his umar even talking
he's unpushed you dog
and you push man
and you push the payload
push the payload
pay attention
by the way
hello
i got it by hard
it's a fight
oh my god
i'm fondly winning
i'm going to get rolled all over
you can someone come help me
i'm stuck by god
okay
Baron does Baron decide
hard it's a fight
i feel like
i was kind of pushing up forward
when you said
this push
because around the corner
was when everyone stayed on the standing
like my friend
i don't trust
i have it
oh my god
why did you hurt
i was going behind them
right
we shall have advantage
we can push
behind for the back piece
back piece
runes left
runes
creeper came back
focus in the hard
nice
die
push
send it
there's a number on here
i can't see you
i'm stuck
for the
help me
i'll kill you
i messed up
good
who's still there
We are not dying there.
No, I just left.
They are not here.
Die!
Oh, that guy switched line.
Okay, I'll switch as well.
Their hands are gonna die.
Reaper behind sir.
Who's one?
He left.
Okay.
Let's go top.
Let's come from here.
Follow me.
Okay, they're trying one.
Die, try one.
We have to go in.
Go ahead.
Let's go.
The Reaper got me.
I can't man.
Okay.
It's good.
It's okay.
It's over.
I can't change it.
That's good.
They're trying to kill me.
Why did they try to kill me?
They're gonna die.
They're trying dead.
He got red.
Nice.